yosto.com 2014-10-03

# Yosto.com - Advanced Lead Generation Affiliate Network

We own, operate and maintain Yosto, which is our Internet property. Yosto is devoted to securing your personal information that you submit via this website. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform our visitors about our practices aimed at protecting their Personally Identifiable Information. This Privacy Policy also contains the information about the choices our visitors can make regarding their Personally Identifiable Information and the way we use it. Prior to start using this website you should review this Privacy Policy that applies to any and all information that is submitted through or collected by Yosto. If you continue using this website and/or register in Yosto, you signify that you have read, understood and agreed with this Privacy Policy in its entirety. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy you should stop using this website and do not register in Yosto.

## Policy on Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information is information about an individual that can help identify or contact them. When you register in Yosto, you provide us with your Personally Identifiable Information, which may include, but is not limited to name, address, birth date, telephone number and email address. Personally Identifiable Information is used by us solely for identification and communication purposes.

## Policy on Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Apart from Personally Identifiable Information, you may also need to provide us with your Non-Personally Identifiable Information, which may include, but is not limited to your IP address, the operating system and browser you are using and your Internet Service Provider.

## Cookies

We use cookies on our website in order to enhance your Yosto using experience. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your computer each time you use this website and make it possible for us to identify you on your next visit. Cookies allow us to store your preferences and use this information to improve our services. You can always disable cookies in your browser’s settings but if you choose to disable them, you may not be able to use this website in full. Please notice that cookies do not provide us with any of your Personally Identifiable Information. Besides, Yosto cannot regulate cookies technology provided by third parties.

## Our Use of Your Information

When you submit any of your Personally Identifiable or Non-Personally Identifiable Information, you agree that we can use this information to send you updates on our products and services, to contact you as a member of Yosto, to send you informational letters about the products and services you may be interested in or to prevent illegal use of Yosto. We can also use your information for the purposes permitted by law and for the purposes you have given your consent to.

## Policy on Information Sharing

We will not normally sell, rent or otherwise share your information with third parties, other than in the cases stated below. We reserve the right to share some of your data with third parties if it is necessary for carrying out payments, billing or deliveries. However, all such parties have contractual obligations to keep your Personally Identifiable Information safe and secure.

We at Yosto are within our rights to share the information you submit via this website when we are subpoenaed or required to do so by law, legal processes or warrants. We are also obligated to share your information when we are asked to do so by a governmental authority, a court or a quasi-governmental authority. We may also share some of your information if you are suspected to be in violation of Yosto’s Privacy Policy and in case we file for bankruptcy or are acquired by a third party. We may also share your personal information to prevent fraud, to solve technical and/or security issues, to improve Yosto design and content, to protect the rights of Yosto and the rights of third parties, or to protect Yosto from incurring liability.

## Information Security

Yosto makes significant efforts to protect your information from any illegal use. We employ a number of security measures, both physical and electronic, designed to protect your data from illicit access, use, sharing or damage both online and offline. Only a limited number of our employees have access to the user’s personal information and their access to such information is limited by strict regulations. Any information transmitted by means of Yosto is secured with Secure Socket Layer encryption. We store our users’ data on secure computers and servers equipped with password protection.

However, we cannot warrant or guarantee that any data transmission or storage is 100% protected, despite all our security measures. If you choose to access and use Yosto and its services, please remember that you are doing so at your own risk.

In case we discover a security breach that may threaten your Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you by email, as well as all relevant regulatory agencies. However, the notification may be delayed if we are asked to do so by a law enforcement agency or in order to determine the scope of the breach and take some immediate measures.

## Storage of Your Personally Identifiable Information

Yosto stores all the information submitted via this website which is necessary to properly render our services, meet legal requirements or resolve disputes. If you do not want us to store your Personally Identifiable Information or want us to update it, you may contact us via any of the contact means listed on our website.

## Opt-Out Rights

If you wish to unsubscribe from our informational messages and offers, you can do it by sending us an email or by following the instructions at the bottom of the emails you receive. Your email will be added to our Suppression list as soon as possible. Please note that you cannot opt out of receiving Yosto’s updates or emails that deal with your participation in our network.

## Third Parties

You can find links to third parties’ websites on Yosto’s site. Please notice that Yosto is on no account responsible for the third parties’ Privacy Policies. This Privacy Policy only regulates your use of Yosto and does not apply to other websites, products or services. Yosto is not responsible for your use of third parties’ websites even if you access them through links on this website.

## Policy on Underage Users

We do not purposefully collect, use or share any information from underage users. You must be at least 18 years of age to have the legal right to use our services. If you have any information about the use of this website by children under 18 please contact us via any of the means listed on our website and we will immediately delete all Personally Identifiable Information submitted by such users from our records.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

We have the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any of these changes by sending you an email. All such changes become effective as soon as they are posted on the website. We encourage you to review Yosto’s Privacy Policy each time you use this website. If you do not agree with any of the changes and/or modification to the Privacy Policy, please stop using this website and our services. If you continue using this website after the changes have become effective, you give your consent to the modified Privacy Policy.

## Titles

This Privacy Policy contains titles and subtitles that are added only for your convenient use of this website. They in no way influence the meaning of this Privacy Policy.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding Yosto’s Privacy Policy, please contact us via any of the means listed in our contact information. We will do our best to respond to you as soon as possible. Thank you for your interest in Yosto!
